{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Bulworth",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty directed the film Bulworth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9235442876815796,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other role did Warren Beatty have in the film Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.876294732093811,
            "question": "Who directed the film Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8375008702278137,
            "question": "Which actor directed the movie Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265270590782166,
            "question": "What type of work did Warren Beatty do in Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.745119035243988,
            "question": "Bulworth is an example of what kind of work by Warren Beatty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7250953912734985,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Warren Beatty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202152609825134,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Warren Beatty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6322273015975952,
            "question": "What was the profession of the person who directed Bulworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5196448564529419,
            "question": "Is Warren Beatty an actor or a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2606080174446106,
            "question": "Warren Beatty is known for what profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty directed the film Bulworth.",
            "html": "yago_21509_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Warren Beatty an actor or a director?",
            "html": "yago_21509_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the profession of the person who directed Bulworth?",
            "html": "yago_21509_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Warren Beatty.",
            "html": "yago_21509_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21509_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because multiple documents mention that Warren Beatty directed the movie Bulworth. For example, in file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21509/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt, it is stated: \"The movie was directed by Warren Beatty, who also played the lead role.\" Additionally, in file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21509/re-ranker-msmarco/100.txt, it is mentioned that Bulworth (which Beatty co-wrote and directed) ...\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Warren Beatty directed the film *Bulworth*, making this statement correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}